It never stops.
The Wind is a horror, mystery, western film directed by Emma Tammi.
Lizzy is a tough, resourceful frontierswoman settling a remote
stretch of land on the 19th-century American frontier.
Isolated from civilization in a desolate wilderness where the wind never stops howling, she begins to sense a sinister presence that seems to be borne of the land
itself, and when a newlywed couple arrive at a nearby homestead, their presence amplifies Lizzy's fears, setting into motion a shocking chain of events.
Lizzy Macklin, played by Caitlin Gerard.
Isaac Macklin, played by Ashley Zukerman.
Emma Harper, played by Julia Goldani Telles.
The Reverend, played by Miles Anderson.
Gideon Harper, played by Dylan McTee.
Eli, played by Martin Patterson.
The Wind is a 2018 American supernatural western horror film directed
by Emma Tammi in her solo feature directorial debut.
It was written by Teresa Sutherland and stars Caitlin Gerard, Ashley
Zukerman, Julia Goldani Telles and Miles Anderson.
The film premiered at the Toronto International
Film Festival on September 10, 2018.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
isolation, pregnancy, paranoia, supernatural.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.